DAVIES ODU

■ daviesodu@gmail.com
daviesodu.com

**** 9848886717

San Francisco, CA

EDUCATION

Springboard, San Mar. 2019 to Apr. Francisco CA 2020

Machine learning Engineer Career Track

Duke University, Aug. 2015 to May Durham NC 2017

Masters Computer Engineering 2017

St Petersburg Sept. 2011 to Electrotechnical, Russia Bachelors Nanotechnology 2015

SUMMARY

I have been moulded into the resilient problem solver and collaborator I am today by my formal and informal education growing up on 3 continents.

My goal is to utilize Al/Machine learning and statistical analysis techniques to drive value while leverage my extensive software development experience gained through numerous roles as a web developer.

SKILLS

MACHINE LEARNING: Deep learning, Feature Engineering, Transfer learning, Classification, Regression, Image Processing, Computer vision

FRAMEWORKS: Tensorflow, Scikit-learn, Keras, Jupyter, Docker, OpenCV

LANGUAGES: Python, Linux, SQL, C#, Typescript

WEB DEVELOPMENT: HTML5, NodeJS, Kusto, GraphQL API

EMPLOYMENT

MICROSOFT

Software Engineer Backend development

RELEAF

Software Engineer API development. Full stack developer.

IBM

Software development

San Francisco June 2017 to Current, June 2017 to Current

Fremont, CA Mar. 2017 to June 2017, Mar. 2017 to June 2017

> RTP Area, Durham NC June 2016 to Dec. 2016

PROJECTS

DEEP FASHION SEARCH ENGINE

 $\label{lem:multi-Class} \mbox{ attribute based classification of clothing images using extracted feature vectors.}$

ARTWORK ATTRIBUTE RECOGNITION

Fine-Grained Visual Categorization of art collection from the New York Metropolitan Museum of Art.

COVID-19 DATA ANALYSIS

Retrieval, processing, modeling and visualization of CORONA Virus data

RECOMMENDATION ENGINE FOR BOOKS

Using item based collaborative filtering to find similar books given a desired book name.

SPRINGBOARD BOOTCAMP

Over 400 hours of hands-on course material, with 1:1 industry expert mentor oversight, and completion of 1 in-depth capstone project. Mastered skills in the machine learning stack, including data wrangling at scale, deep learning, and building and deploying large-scale AI systems

AWARDS

Microsoft Silicon Valley · MICROSOFT GLOBAL HACKATHON 2019

Most collaborative project, put together a team of 50 from 5 continents

VOLUNTEERING

OPEN DATA SCIENCE CONFERENCE · Volunteer Staff

San Mateo

Renowned Al conference. Emceed on second largest stage. Kept the audience engaged and introduced Al game changers on stage.

SILICON VALLEY FORUM · Technical Mentor

San Francisco

A special hackathon that invites the best and brightest minds to innovate solutions targeted towards growing food on Mars.

CAL HACKS · Microsoft Technical Mentor University of California, Berkeley

A special nackation that invites the best and brightest minus to innovate solutions targeted towards growing room

Oct. 2017

Cal Hacks brings together 1,700 hackers from 100 schools and 5 countries to innovate in a fun atmosphere.

0.1.0010

Nov. 2017

Oct. 2019